rhinoshield.io 2019-02-26

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from rhinoshield.io (the “Site”).

\-----

PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information”. We collect Device Information using the following technologies:   
\- “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.   
\- “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.   
\- “Web beacons”, “tags”, and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, PayPal account), email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information”.

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

\-----

HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:   
\- Communicate with you;   
\- Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and   
\- When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

Fraud prevention and detection:   
We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address).

Marketing Communications:   
We may use your information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communication form us by following the unsubscribe link or contact us any time at support@evolutivelabs.com.

Behavioural Advertising:   
We use the Device Information to serve you advertisements regarding products or marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you. The information may also be used for frequency capping purposes (e.g., to ensure we do not display the same advertisement to you repeatedly) and to help us regulate the advertisements you receive and measure their effectiveness. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

Performance and Analytics:   
We use the Device Information to analyse how the our service is accessed, is used, or is performing. We use this information to maintain, operate, and continually improve our service. We may also obtain information from our email newsletters, including whether you opened or forwarded a newsletter or clicked on any of its content. This information tells us about our newsletters' effectiveness and helps us ensure that we're delivering information that you find interesting.

\-----

SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We share your Personal Information with the following trusted third party service providers to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. 

Shopify:   
We use Shopify to power our online store--you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy.

LinkShare (Rakuten Marketing LLC):   
LinkShare uses cookies to anonymously record that a user has clicked on a Linkshare link that referred the user to this site. This information is collected in order to enable us to pay a commission to Linkshare and its affiliates for any sales they may drive on this site. You can read more about their Privacy Policy here: https://rakutenmarketing.com/legal-notices

Google Analytics:   
It helps us understand how our customers use the Site -- you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

Facebook Pixel and Facebook Custom Audiences:   
We use Facebook Pixel and Facebook Custom Audiences to deliver advertisements to Site visitors on Facebook based on your shopping experience. These tools allows us to track user behavior and display interest-based and personalized ads to you when you are using Facebook or its related platforms. The collected data remain anonymous. This means that we cannot see the personal data of any individual user. You can opt-out of Facebook advertising here: https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads

Google AdWords:   
We use Google AdWrods to deliver advertisements to Site visitors on Google network. Each AdWords customer receives a different conversion cookie. The information collected by the cookie is used to generate conversion statistics. Again, the collected data remain anonymous and we do not receive any information that personally identifies any individual user. You can opt-out of Google AdWords advertising here: https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous

You can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.

We also use the following third-party service providers: Boltics Core XYZ, Bulk Discounts, Bulk Fulfilment, CBC, Crazy Egg, Edit Order by Cleverfic, Form Builder, Google Shopping, Gorgias, Mailchimp for Shopify, MassFulfil, Order Printer, Privy, Script Editor, Shopify Flow, SumAll and Zendesk.

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

\-----

DO NOT TRACK

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

\-----

YOUR RIGHTS

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.   
Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

\-----

DATA RETENTION

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

\-----

CHANGES

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

\-----

CONTACT US

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by email at support@evolutivelabs.com.
